Hey! Lady Paladin! Looks like your armor's pretty busted!
You want me to fix that for you? I'll give you a discount if you're a beginner.
My name is Rudy Hime. It's nice to meet you, Lady Paladin.
There's something that I wanted to talk to you about. Is that okay?
Where am I?
What a surprise.
Here, I thought you were going to confess your love for me.
Oh, sorry. Was I giving off that vibe?
Well, you weren't giving off any other vibes.
My bad.
So, what did you want to tell me?
Uh, well, you see...
Akane says that she's fallen in love with someone!
Hey, no way! Good for you!
Shall I guess who it is?
Don't say it.
This is quite the touching scenario.
When I first met you in game, Akanechi,
you were tottering about all alone
and seemingly having no fun at all.
Now that I think about it,
you were probably a mess after just getting dumped.
But now, you're back on your feet.
Good job.
But she's still trying to figure out
why she got dumped and she's agonizing over it!
Huh? That's so negative!
What are you doing that for?
Um, it may sound that way
when you put it like that,
but I just want to know
if there's something I've been doing wrong
this whole time.
In my head,
I'm thinking about things positively.
That's why...
You see...
I mean, it's just that...
Whenever I see your face, Eita,
it makes me want to talk to Rurihime too.
Because the ones who comforted me
when things were tough
were Momo and Rurihime.
So I wanted to tell both of you
that I've fallen in love.
Uh-huh.
I know the guy you've fallen for.
I have for a long time.
And he's great.
People tend to only talk about his looks,
but I've never met anyone as kind as he is.
Well, you already knew that,
but...
It really is true.
He's an insensitive guy
with a big heart.
So you can just be yourself.
Being too straightforward
is exactly what he needs.
So go for it!
Momo and I are here if he rejects you.
He's right, you know, Akane.
You have to be bold
and take action
once your mind's made up!
You might as well
confess your feelings right now!
You said it, Momo!
Oh, Momo!
Fine!
I'll take my chances
and go for broke!
Ooh!
Don't get too broken, okay?
I'll try really hard not to.
Mm-hmm!
Thanks, you two!
I love you both so much!
Hmm.
I just hope she doesn't get broken at all.
Yeah, well,
who knows how it'll go.
Oh, by the way,
hello again!
I'm Momoko Maeda.
And I'm Eita Sasaki.
I'm a 20-year-old college student
who's seriously looking for a husband.
Do you have a girlfriend?
When was it
that I fell in love with him?
Try as I might,
I can't really remember.
but
since he doesn't smile a lot,
it made me happy
whenever he did smile.
Trying to pretend
that I didn't notice,
telling myself
we were just friends.
All my efforts
to brush it off,
they really didn't mean much.
Oh,
I'm so sorry!
I'm panicking too much.
Are you okay?
I'll be okay now.
Yes?
Okane?
Um,
hi!
Hello.
So,
uh,
what are you doing here?
Well,
you see,
if you have a moment,
there's something
I need to talk to you about.
Is it already time for your walk?
I, um...
It's already about
that time for you
to take your walk!
Huh?
Oh, hi!
It's warm out here!
I'll tell you what!
Yes, sir!
It's wet!
Today, isn't it?
Now,
if only it could be
warm and toasty
like this!
I mean...
Oh, I know, that's right!
It really is
warm outside today.
Akane?
Yes?
Sorry to stop you,
but I have to be
leaving for cram school
in a minute.
Oh, you do?
Sorry,
I thought you'd be
off on Saturdays.
I can listen
to what you have to say,
but can it be
on the way
to the station?
I mean,
couldn't we have
done this over the phone?
Dummy.
Obviously,
Yamada has his own schedule.
You didn't even
think of that.
I'm sorry.
I'll come back
another...
I'm gonna go change.
So if you could
wait a sec.
Uh, sure.
Sorry again
for bothering you
while you're busy.
That startled me.
By the way,
seems like your cold
is gone.
Uh, yeah, it is,
thanks to you.
By the way,
I...
I'll just look this way.
Thank you for waiting.
So,
what's this about?
Sorry.
I'm trying to figure out
how to bring it up
right now.
There's no time.
I've got to say it.
That's why I came here
after all.
But still,
there's no reason
why I should rush
to tell him
everything now.
Especially when
we're in the street
and things are so hectic.
Another day.
When we have more time.
Akane!
Didn't you see?
The light was red.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Are you alright?
You seem really
spaced out today.
It's no good.
I have no focus.
Sorry.
Even if I just
buy myself time
being with him,
I'm only causing
trouble for Yamada.
It can wait.
On second thought,
I'll tell you it...
It's green.
Maybe I'll just
let myself
give in to
his kindness forever
and not say
anything I shouldn't.
But hiding
my feelings like that
would kind of
be unfair to him.
Alright then.
I'm getting on
the train now.
Okay.
I know we didn't
get a chance
to talk.
Sorry.
I was rushing
because I'm running
kind of late.
It's not you.
I think there was
just something wrong
with me.
Yeah, you're right
about that.
Well, another time
then.
Mm-hmm.
Is it something important?
After class, I...
I mean, it's gonna be
late, but...
I can call if
that's okay with you.
If it's something
you want to tell me
today.
Are you sure?
Won't you be tired?
Just listening
won't be a problem.
Though I'm not
exactly sure if I'll
be a good person
to talk to.
Okay.
Cool.
Later then.
Have a good one.
Good luck with your class.
The weather turned nasty
all of a sudden,
didn't it?
The sun was literally
just out.
That's it for tonight.
Make sure you do
the writing exercises
on your own, okay?
Rain, huh?
Just great.
Hey, yo, Yamada.
How you battling
this downpour?
I brought one of those
fold-up umbrellas with me.
Oh, my God!
Wanna share your umbrella
with me?
Sure thing.
Hey, Prez,
will you be okay?
I don't have an umbrella,
but I suppose
I'll be running home.
Isn't that a little
too daring of you?
Ah, what the heck.
I'll give up my spot
under Yamada's umbrella
for you, Prez.
Are you cool
with that, Yamada?
Either one of you
is fine.
Huh?
But I'd feel bad.
Why don't you two
just go?
Nah, how could I
put my own needs
over the head of a lady's?
In this way,
you can go home together
so you should pounce.
I don't need you
to look out for me
like that, you know?
Yamada will think
I'm a weirdo.
Don't you know
you'll never get
anywhere with him
unless you come off
as a little weird?
Especially you.
They can't settle it
because they're trying
to give it up
to each other?
Maybe I'll just
give them my umbrella
and make a run for it.
Yamada?
Hmm?
Hey, uh...
on second thought
we could share
your umbrella
until we get
to the station
if that's cool.
Oh yeah.
I decided to try
that new game.
It's still in beta
right now
so it's pretty buggy.
But it looks like
it'll be really good.
Hurry up!
Just wait!
You're so slow, Saki.
My shoes are slippery.
Such bad weather.
Do you know that person?
Who?
Right there.
Because your eyes
were following her
when she ran by just now.
I don't know her.
Uh, Tsubaki.
Here.
Please take this
for yourself after all.
Huh?
How come?
It would defeat the purpose
if you got wet.
So please.
But why?
What about you?
I'll make a run for it.
The station's right there.
Um...
Wait, I...
Wait!
Please wait!
Yamada!
Stop!
Please!
I'm sorry.
My glasses...
I can't see.
They're broken.
Are you okay?
I like you.
What?
Sorry to put you on the spot.
I like you.
But...
Please.
Just for today.
I want you to try
thinking of me.
It can just be for today.
Oh...
What's the time?
You know, it was raining really hard yesterday, huh?
It was so loud, it woke me up right out of my sleep.
And then, I couldn't sleep a wink after that.
You're not concentrating at all, are you, Runa?
Nope, not anymore.
Good work, studying so hard.
I brought you some donuts, so please have some, you two.
Donuts!
I really appreciate you taking time out of your own studies to help her, Yamada.
When we were looking for a tutor, Runa insisted she didn't want anyone but you.
She must really adore you.
But I have to say, seeing the two of you together like this, you make such a nice couple.
Isn't that right, son?
You're getting pretty bold there, Mom.
Not hiding your ambitions even a little.
What do you mean?
Who knows?
All I'm saying is that those two would make quite the sweet couple, if you say so, Mom.
Do you know what they're talking about?
No clue.
Must be some kind of joke, maybe?
By the way, Akito, that reminds me.
Someone confessed to you yesterday, didn't they?
How did you know?
I know everything, okay?
So Akanechi really confessed, huh?
That girl's amazing.
So, what'd you do?
How'd you respond?
That's none of your concern.
It is, though.
It is, huh?
I'm still thinking.
Ah, is that so?
I was sure you were actually gonna go for it, though.
Huh.
Since you're so close.
Wow.
You really are vague, my guy.
You should give her your answer sooner than later and be clear about it.
Being suggestive with someone and then toying with them is the worst thing you could do.
I'd never do that.
Stupid Eita made Yamada mad again.
I'm sorry, Akun.
Take these donuts.
Please don't be mad.
These donuts are runes.
The number you are trying to reach is out of signal range or has been turned off.
Please hang up and try again.
Oh.
Akane.
Look who's waiting outside.
Hey, Yamada!
What are you doing here?
It's kinda unusual for you to stop by our store.
Aren't you supposed to be working?
I asked to do some outside work.
Now then, have you come to see me?
I'm just kidding.
That's right.
Huh?
I did try calling you, but it didn't go through.
Oh, you did, huh?
Sorry about that.
My battery was already down to 3% when I left my apartment.
That's okay.
I just thought if I could see you in person, I could apologize for yesterday.
No.
Oh.
I don't mind at all.
It wasn't really important anyway.
And come to think of it, I've already talked to Momo about it, so...
I've pretty much gotten it off my chest, I guess.
But never mind that.
You seem a little down today.
What's wrong?
Do I?
I'm feeling pretty normal.
Huh?
You're so not like you.
Your voice has no energy.
Well, that's always the case.
You're also not very talkative.
I guess you never are, though.
You're usually like this.
But today, you're like this.
Hmm?
I guess I've been a little busy, so maybe I'm tired.
Studying for entrance exams must be draining.
That's tough.
His problems are on a whole different planet than mine.
I see.
Oh, hey, I forgot to tell you.
I recently got some new gear in FOS.
I've been dying to brag about it to you, but you never seem to log in these days.
I got myself a sweet new sword.
What kind of sword?
What kind?
Meaning...
You know, like the weapon rank or type.
Uh, let's see.
Give me your hand.
Is that permanent?
Those bosses sure drop some great items, don't they?
I've been wondering why you're always raiding bosses, but I think I finally get it now.
Well, yeah, though the odds of a drop are slim.
I know, right?
So when a decent item does end up dropping, it makes you feel outrageously happy.
It's exhilarating.
I don't know what's going on, but it will pass.
Then you can go back to being your mysterious self.
So that's how I look to people.
I'm usually quiet because I'm scared I'll say the wrong thing, so I say nothing.
I'm not very good at reading into other people's feelings.
And most of the time, their jokes go right over my head.
I know that I'm boring.
It's obvious.
Hmm.
If you ask me, you know how you sometimes set me straight in that astute way of yours?
I really like that.
And when you're with us, you don't say much, but I know you're looking out for everyone.
Also, I know you always try to help people out if they're in trouble.
Because you've already done that for me so many times.
And you're not boring at all.
Like I said, you're fun.
Trust me on that.
I mean it.
Okay?
When I wake up, I let out a sigh.
Somewhere along the way, that became a habit of mine.
I was so sure.
Yukari, you're going out at this hour?
Just for a bit. I'm supposed to meet up with a friend.
Well, come home as soon as you can, okay?
Yeah.
That love was supposed to be more fun than this.
Thank you.